Viewers all over the world, we have received the Word of God.
I pray the Word finds a place in your heart, in Jesus Christ's name!
Our heart is of faith. Man's heart is of faith.
I pray once again that the Word finds a place in your heart, in Jesus' name!
In Jesus' name!
Feeding on the Word makes our way plain before us.
When you feed on the Word of God, your way is plain!
Greater is He that is in you.
Read your Bible with devotion because it is food for your soul.
Viewers, tell your neighbour, "Read your Bible with devotion because it is food for your soul".
It is food for my soul.
It is well
With my soul
Read it because it is your spiritual weapon.
It is your spiritual weapon.
Read your Bible because it has a purifying power.
It has a purifying power.
Read your Bible because it has healing power.
It is so profitable.
Read your Bible.
It is enduring.
It keeps us from sin and error.
For me, I meditate on what I read in the Scripture day by day - without ceasing
and whatever I do, whatever I say, whatever I think prospers.
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Those who are under the influence of this telecast, right now,
I can sense God touching you.
Be touched, in the name of Jesus!
I can sense God touching you, right now.
Believe!
Let every spirit operating in your life, career, future, family begin to leave you,
in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
All spirits operating in your life,
operating in your career,
operating in your business,
operating in your marital life,
operating in your family,
begin to leave, in the name of Jesus!
I command - leave!
Leave my people!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
You must leave!
Leave my people, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
You are the head, not the tail.
All spirits operating in your life, begin to leave, in the name of Jesus!
Be it in your business, career, marriage, I command you to leave, in the name of Jesus!
Leave, in the name of Jesus!
Yes!
At the command of Jesus, blind Bartimaeus regained his sight.
I command healing on you, in the name of Jesus!
Wherever it is located, that affliction,
be it in your bones, kidneys, blood, liver, fluids - I command them to cease, in the name of Jesus!
Leave!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Yes, your body is a temple of God, not a temple of affliction.
temple of our flesh
You need peace - peace of heart for your salvation.
Say, "I need peace - peace of heart for my salvation".
Leave my people, in the name of Jesus!
Wherever that affliction, sickness is located, I command you to leave, in the name of Jesus!
I command you to leave, in the name of Jesus!
I can hear "Breakthrough" in your business.
I can hear "Breakthrough" in your career.
I can hear "Breakthrough".
Breakthrough!
This is what I hear from God concerning your business, "Breakthrough!"
This is what I hear from God about your business, about someone here.
Breakthrough!
In the name of Jesus!
From above!
Breakthrough!
The way out for you has come!
Say, "The way out for me has come!"
The way out for my business has come!
The way out for my career has come!
The way out for my marriage has come!
The way out for my health has come!
Thank You, Jesus!